Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever!
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever!
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
This is a baffling bombshell
to that Alto battle, folks!
It appears that all twenty-something
remaining brawlers have
somehow been knocked unconscious
What is this twist of events?
I have never seen anything like this in
the history of the Corridor Coliseum,
ladies and gentlemen.
What's this?
Do my eyes deceive me?
I think I can make out the figure
of someone struggling to stand up.
Could this potentially be our winner?
Is this the fighter responsible
for our shock and awe?
What?
Rebecca?
Rebecca is our lone survivor?
Folks,
we have seen a spectacular showcase of fan
favorites and behemoth frontrunners today.
Yet, shockingly, not one remains standing.
The contestant who will be
moving into the final round.
And our Corita Battle
Tournament block D winner is,
Unbelievably, from the bloodline of the
disgraced King Rick, the prisoner gladiator,
Rebecca!
I don't understand how she did it.
All I noticed was a cloud of
dust, then everyone went belly up.
Do the details really matter here, boys?
Rebecca gets to move on to the next round!
I can't believe this! She cheated!
She made Cavendish? No way!
I call shenanigans!
Admiral O 'Lumbus wouldn't lose to her!
It was the slicing winds of Rommel.
What's that, sir?
You don't know?
There was quite the story.
Years ago, there was an odd
phenomenon tormenting Rommel.
It was said that late at night,
terrorizing gusts of wind would slice right
through the kingdom's innocent citizens.
A naval unit was dispatched
to investigate the issue.
But unfortunately these wins also claimed
the lives of a few good men that day.
However, we did come to learn the
cause of that dreadful cutting zephyr?
Disturbingly,
it was a human responsible for the callous
attacks—a man who referred
to himself as Akuba.
akuba
Regrettably to this very day,
the fiend remains at large.
Even after the incident in Rommel Kingdom,
there have been similar reports
of Hakuba in other regions.
And wherever Hakuba has been sighted,
there just so happens to be another
pirate around at the same time.
What?
You did not steal my blade wench!
Out of my way!
Is something wrong with him?
He fell asleep?
Oh, my God.
He's a sleepwalker, correct.
Hakuba only awakens while
Cavendish is fast asleep.
One could even refer to
him as a sort of alter ego,
although it's technically
Hakuba who killed people.
Cavendish had no other choice but
to become a pirate as a consequence;
I kind of feel bad for the poor bastard.
Don't waste your pity on him.
The fool relishes in the
notoriety this brings him.
Indulge in sympathy and he
might best you, yes, sir.
He is already a prodigy
swordsman as is but
Hakuba's skills could
put Cavendishes to shame.
Of course, he still has to fall
asleep to have his alter ego appear,
so as you can imagine,
that doesn't always play out as
planned, especially in a battle royale.
There's no way Rebecca won this Serger;
I'm sure she has a best.
Hot damn, she dominated that
without landing a single blow.
Always more than one way to win a fight.
Also,
I don't think it came
down to just luck either,
as she was the only one to
see through Hakuba's attacks.
Anyway,
no matter who the winner may be,
I can't let them get their
hands on the flame flame fruit.
Goody, I was getting antsy!
The finals are finally here!
See that, old man?
Your granddaughter sure is
lucky, if I do say so myself.
Who'd have guessed that
this little fighting
tournament would become a family affair?
Your Majesty, what happened?
Willing to throw some elbows for
a bite of Devil Fruit, are we?
Look how low the mighty hath fallen.
Rebecca.
You know something?
I noticed that your entire family
has been acting a bit off today.
And that includes sweet
little Violet's betrayal.
I don't really believe in coincidences.
I shouldn't have to explain my motive.
But the actions you took this morning.
We journeyed to your island to
address rumors concerning Doflamingo's
abdication of the throne and
retirement from the Seven Warlords.
It was a false report.
Simply a mistake.
It reignited my passion
to want to stand up and
fight for everything in
the kingdom once more.
That was all.
Isn't that heroic?
Still trying to earn the
people's favor after so long.
But Viola must have her own motivations.
Unlike you, she would never be
caught acting on her emotions alone.
A cunning and calculating tramp, that one.
Bet she's weighing eruptions now.
She put so much stock in this rookie.
But look what's become of him.
The warlord.
Trafalgar Law.
And that boy, who became famous two years
ago with the demon blood in his veins.
How pathetic.
I imagine the ignorant shrew was banking
on those two heroes to strike me down cold.
Yet here's law, barely clinging to life.
And Straw Hat will never
get to leave the Coliseum.
Not as a human being, at least.
As of right now,
the only member of the Straw Hat crew
who's doing anything is that cyborg Franky,
who's reportedly attacking the
toy house unassisted as we speak.
But I have faith my family
executives will take care of him.
His other allies, the pirate hunter Zoro,
Firefox Kin'emon, Niko Robin,
and Sniper King remain at large.
but i highly doubt they can get
anywhere near my underground factory
job down here is pretty easy you
just keep all these toys and lies
yeah that's it seems simple enough
but i really don't know much about
this stuff so you think you can show
me i learned better from example
there's gonna be a lift just up ahead
Okay, listen carefully.
The palace where Doflamingo
is lurking, the toy house,
and the treeport where the Smile
Factory is located are all connected.
In other words, infiltrating the palace
allows us to ingress the other locations?
That's right.
To get access to the factory,
you have to either pass through the
palace or enter through the toy house.
The only other way inside
is through the trade
port in a secret tunnel
that my people and I dug.
The most direct route for us
to take is through the palace.
Very well, understood.
Although I'm still in a state
of disbelief over such we folk,
in spite of one standing
before my very eyes.
Yeah, these guys are great, huh?
She's like a toy!
We're told that we shouldn't.
We're only supposed to allow the big
people of the royal family to see us.
But you guys, the Straw Hat Usulunders
are the exception to that rule.
Usulunders?
There's no time to explain
all the details now.
Operation SOP is already underway.
Okay, you can see it there.
That's the lift entrance to the
palace I was telling you about.
The only problem is, to use the lift, we
have to show a pass to a security guard.
Let's just kick his butt. No!
No!
If you make a huge scene, it'll
just bring us unnecessary attention!
Somebody's there!
You want something?
Are you Straw Hat Luffy?
Yeah, what's up? Don't tell her!
Come with me.
I'm here to help guide
you into the palace.
Now, time for the final round!
have shockingly announced their
withdrawal from the competition.
I am at a loss here, folks.
My apologies.
Don't fret.
We've got a treat in store.
Subbing in is none other
than our Coliseum's hero,
Mr. Diamante!
He will be showing up in the finals
and throwing down on their stead.
Diamante!
Oh, Diamante!
Take him to the medical room.
Hurry!
Lucy!
I'm in the finals, too!
Lucy?
It's not him.
Not cool!
What makes you think you're worthy
of speaking to him like that?
Oh, you must be Rebecca.
I'm actually rather familiar
with your backstory.
I'm going to cause a bit
of commotion here shortly.
But I swear I won't do you wrong.
It's all about putting on
appearances around here.
There's something about this kingdom.
I can't help but think
of the place I grew up.
We've caught wind that one needs
a sort of pass to enter the lift.
While the lift would take you directly
to the palace entrance, it's too risky.
If they find out who
you are, it's all over.
And more importantly...
Please, proceed.
You look suspicious.
Madam, I'm offended.
Aren't you the one who lured
our idiot cook-away earlier?
Sanji?
There you are.
Oh!
Violet, my sweet!
Yes, and he hurried off
to protect your ship.
Uh-huh, we knew the rest.
So you were the one who told him
the Sonny was in trouble, huh?
Then perchance did you provide Sir Sanji
with the map to the toy house as well?
Yes, that was me.
How did you acquire such an item?
I was one of Doflamingo's
subordinates. What?
For real? It's true!
But she was only
pretending to be a bad guy!
Wicca, it's you! Huh?
Wow, you actually remember me?
Come now, did you forget about my ability?
I've been keeping a close watch
on your people this entire time.
I also know about the plan.
You're fighting alongside the brave,
one-legged soldier who's been looking
after Rebekah since my sister passed away.
King Rick will return to the throne.
You've been working so hard.
Thank you for still
believing in my father.
Princess Yola!
Huh?
So wait, you're a princess?
Could you turn it down a little?
I used to be.
If Rebecca's the king's granddaughter,
that makes you... what now?
Rebecca is my niece.
She's the daughter of my
late older sister, Scarlet.
A hidden door.
Are you a ninja?
Now I've seen everything.
A princess and a ninja.
remarkable
this
is a
secret escape passage
of the Rick family not even
Doflamingo knows that it's here
what
is this
comically large baskets purpose it's a
pulley for lifting cargo look up hmm
looks like it reaches all the way to the
top and i spy a fine staircase as well
now if you follow the flight of steps
up you'll reach the rampart tower
where the entrance is located uh luffy
how about you make this easy on everyone
and grab this boulder here and shoot
yourself up oh quite a novel solution if
you can bring the chains once atop and
cascade back down we can traverse upwards
with ease that sounds like Madness.
Okay, here it goes.
Make it snappy, Luffy.
Please join us for the
ride upward, Madam Ninja.
No way. What?
Come on, what is this crap?
I've had enough!
Franky Rocket!
Wait for it!
Launcher!
Get away!
That guy is crazy!
I thought it was launch from the cannon
on his head, but I guess not, huh?
Ah!
Senor, get out of there!
Come on, use your dive ability!
You can clean your teeth with
a shoe shine brush later!
No way!
He's such a hard-boiled guy!
Senor!
Senor Pink, no!
Senor Pink!
Senor!
Why didn't you use your
powers to dodge that?
You shouldn't make blind
assumptions about others, you pumps.
I use my swim-swim-fruit
powers on my own terms.
Yes, I can move through walls and floors.
But under no circumstances ever will
I use it to run away from the enemy.
In other words...
I'll go for a swim when I feel like it.
He's got to ramble!
Huh?
Is that brandy?
Oh, he's bleeding all over.
I think he broke a bone or two.
He's cleansing his wounds with brandy?
I see now.
Huh?
Señor, you're way too good for this world.
You've put your life at
risk and taken a hit head-on
because you knew your calling
was incapacitated behind you.
My tummy's hurting.
My heart can't take it.
Señor, I would die for you.
That was a long time ago.
Don't dwell on the past.
Make love to me, Señor.
Hey, Vice, can you stand up?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
Damn, that guy's hard-boiled as hell.
Oh, my dum-tum, the pain!
Oh, no, must have missed a gain!
Quit moving around like
some vermin, dang it!
Shut up, man!
What the super hell is with you guys?!
Stop right there!
Cyborg Franky and the Straw Hat Pirates?!
We'll be seizing the toy house, so
better surrender to us now! Huh?
Why's the Navy interfering? What's that?
Did I just miss something?
I don't recall ordering more trouble.
I'm thrilled you made the
right choice, Fujitora.
Smart man.
Well, I'm not ready to declare where I
stand in these complicated matters just yet.
We can't take risks with Straw Hat
afoot and with other suspicious
parties getting involved—considered
a precautionary measure,
our choice was made for us.
The
navy's primary priority is to curtail the
suffering of small folk in this scuffle.
If
Straw Hat's intention is to take you down,
then I'd wager he'd do
that with little little
regard for anything or anyone in his path.
And if my sense of justice is correct,
those humble folks will need my assistance.
Once that is settled, I'll be
taking care of you personally.
Now I may be a newcomer to this game,
recruited through the world military draft,
but since I was appointed to
the position of navy admiral,
I've got put a simple goal in
mind till I bear witness to
the complete abolition of this
accursed seven warlord system.
A time back there was a
pirate who came in like a ball
of fire and attempted to force
his will over some kingdom;
I reckon if he had his way, that land
would be in a similar state as this one.
What do you think will happen
to the balance of power?
No clue, we won't figure that
out till it's demolished.
However, if you keep up this
foolish reign of terror,
the
price
on your head
will only increase.
Heavenly demon, did I mishear you?
I thought you said, "off me."
Now, while you have the chance,
let's not be hasty; we can operate
under a gentleman's agreement.
My only objective is to
protect your kingdom,
so any sort of rough edges that
I may accidentally happen upon,
I promise to turn a blind eye too,
and rest assured that's the
only kind of eye I have.
Don't forget that we have the reverie
world summit coming up this year.
This world's going to be changing,
whether you like it or not.
The Corridor Coliseum Battle
Tournament continues on!
At last, the final round!
Just in time!
Everyone in the kingdom is watching as
we lock the special ring into place now!
We will soon find out when our
final five contenders duke it out!
Not gonna lie, I'm pretty excited.
Well, let's get to it, Marine Coliseo.
What did you call me?
It's Bartolomeo, man.
Look, our first contender
is marching in now.
Oh boy, it's our surprise fightless
and wayward wanderer, none other
than
I
hope
you're watching over me,
Ace.